Citizens!
War is raging, and invaders
have surrounded our country!
Yet our Great Leader is doing nothing
but searching for traitors
in his attempt to cling to power!
The state constantly feeds us false propaganda,
claiming the Motherland is in danger,
and the party-controlled mass media
call for workers and farmers
to find spies among their family members!
It's time to say no
to their ongoing oppression!
Hundreds of thousands of laborers
have answered our call,
and are assisting the Revolution
and the arrival of a New Tomorrow!
Our country is falling apart,
and our people are starving!
Our motto is your clarion call:
Muster all of your strength to fight the real enemy –
the tyranny of the so-called Great Leader!
Join the movement toward a New Tomorrow!
Let the voice of truth
be heard across the land!