Hello, little one!
Today, we will tell you
a wise tale of three piglets.
Once upon a time, there was a huge apartment
complex managed by the Grey Wolf.
Three piglets, all of whom were brothers, lived there.
Their names were Nih-Nih,
Nah-Nah, and Nuh-Nuh.
Nih-Nih was very poor:
he slept on a straw mattress
and used a rag nailed
to the wall instead of a door.
This little piglet had a dairy in which
he recorded all of his troubles with the landlord.
He was sure his home
was his fortress,
and believed nobody
would ever find his book.
Nah-Nah had more than his brother.
He had a real bed, and his door
was made of plywood and had a latch.
At night, Nah-Nah liked to
experiment with his radio.
In time, he was able to tune into a foreign
radio station prohibited by the Grey Wolf.
Nuh-Nuh, the oldest, loved his life.
He had a king-size bed
and a sturdy oak door
with a huge iron lock.
He worked in the Ministry of Groceries,
and lived high on the hog,
selling stolen food to his brothers.
Then came the day when
the Grey Wolf ran out of patience.
He pulled aside the little brother's rag,
knocked out the middle one's plywood door,
and unlocked the oldest one's oak door.
Then he took the fat, lazy piglets to the factory
to be turned into delicious sausages.
He then gave the links
to the other tenants -
the very ones who had diligently watched and reported
the activities of the piglets to the Grey Wolf.
All this happened because the piglets forgot
who gave them everything they had.
So remember, little one, it doesn't matter
how you live: the landlord sees it all!
Just be happy you don't get sausages
for dinner too often;
in means we don't have many
traitors among us!